question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In the Season One Championship of League of Legends, the highest achievable rank was Diamond.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Sports",
        "question": "During Wimbledon, spectators in the grounds can buy the tennis balls that have been used in matches.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In &quot;League of Legends&quot;, there exists four different types of Dragon.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "Is Tartu the capital of Estonia?",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
        "question": "In &quot;Avatar: The Last Airbender&quot; and &quot;The Legend of Korra&quot;, Lavabending is a specialized bending technique of Firebending.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "The band &quot;Panic! At the Disco&quot; has released 4 albums total",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Sports",
        "question": "Tennis was once known as Racquetball.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "question": "The original ending of &quot;Little Shop Of Horrors&quot; has the plants taking over the world.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]
